[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "How many oscars did the Titanic movie got?",
   "Answer": "Eleven"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "How many Tomb Raider movies were made?",
   "Answer": "Two movies"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Which malformation did Marilyn Monroe have when she was born?",
   "Answer": "Six toes"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "What is the house number of the Simpsons?",
   "Answer": "Number 742"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the prison in the film The Rock?",
   "Answer": "Alcatraz"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the protagonist in the Last Action Hero film?",
   "Answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "What is the pseudonym of Allen Stewart Koningsberg?",
   "Answer": "Woody Allen"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the little dragon in the animated movie Mulan?",
   "Answer": "Mushu"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor does play Sonny Crockett in Miami Vice 2006?",
   "Answer": "Colin Farell"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the director of Reservoir Dogs?",
   "Answer": "Quentin Tarantino"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the director of the X-files?",
   "Answer": "Rob Bowman"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the male protagonist in The Horse Wisperer?",
   "Answer": "Robert Redford"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "Who did play the role of Peter Pan in the Peter Pan movie?",
   "Answer": "Robin Williams"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "Which Italian film director is considered as the father of the spaghetti western?",
   "Answer": "Sergio Leone"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "What number is on Herbie the beatle?",
   "Answer": "Fifty-three"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "Give the name of the best James Bond parody.",
   "Answer": "Austin Powers"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the bald commander of the Enterprise in Star Trek?",
   "Answer": "Captain Picard"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of Steven Spielberg s black-and-white-film about the second world war?",
   "Answer": "Schindler s List"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the leading actress in Sister act I en II ?",
   "Answer": "Whoopi Goldberg"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What is the profession of Popeye?",
   "Answer": "Seaman"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the director of the movie The Piano?",
   "Answer": "Jane Campion"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "Who was Mozart s great rival in Amadeus movie?",
   "Answer": "Antonio Salieri"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "Which French woman was the most famous actress in the world in the late 19th and early 20th century?",
   "Answer": "Sarah Bernhardt"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "Who played the lead role in the movie Scarface in 1983?",
   "Answer": "Al Pacino"
 },
 {
   "No": 25,
   "Quiz question": "Who played Che Guevara in the movie \"Evita\"?",
   "Answer": "Antonio Banderas"
 }
]